hungry-girl.com 2019-12-15

# Hungry Girl

Hungry Girl takes very seriously the private nature of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit our Web site and/or register for your daily email.

 **Personal Information**  
In order to send you your Hungry Girl info we need your e-mail address. So that we may provide you with additional services, we may also request your name, geographical coordinates, and telephone number. Hungry Girl does not collect any other personal information that you do not expressly provide. Hungry Girl will not disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, except to a third party as required to help us send your information to you.

**Non-Personal Information**  
We may also request non-personally identifiable information, such as annual income, buying preferences, or age, also known as demographic and profile data, though this information is optional. We may use this data to improve our site and/or tailor your experience at our site, showing you content that we think you might be interested in, and displaying content according to your preferences. We may also share this information with others, such as advertisers interested in advertising with Hungry Girl or our site, in aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the information will not contain any personally identifiable information about you or any other person.

**Usage Information**  
In addition to collecting personal and non-personal information, Hungry Girl may also collect non-personal, aggregated information about subscribers' use of our site. This information is not personally identifiable and will only be used to find out how subscribers use our service and site. For example, this information will tell us how much time users spend on our site, from which other sites subscribers came, and to what other sites subscribers go. The collection of this information allows us to, among other things, prepare for traffic load demands and to efficiently deliver content to you.

**Review and Access**  
Upon your request, we will provide you with a summary of the information we collect about you. You will have an opportunity to correct, update or modify this information.

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
If we ever send you information by e-mail concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an e-mail address by which you may request no future notices.

**Cookies**  
Like most sites Hungry Girl makes use of browser "cookies." Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard disk by our server. They allow us to quickly check your status as a subscriber and facilitate access to your preferences. Hungry Girl will never use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to our site or services.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Hungry Girl may create links allowing you to access third party sites. Hungry Girl is not responsible for the content that appears on those sites and does not endorse these sites. Please consult those sites' individual privacy policies in order to determine how they treat user information.

**Security**  
All information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

**The Hungry Girl Diet App**  
The Hungry Girl Diet App does not collect or share any user information.

**Ad Services**  
Hungry Girl is a member of the SHE Media Partner Network, and ads displayed on the website are served through SHE Media. You can [access the privacy policy here](http://corporate.shemedia.com/faq/ad-services-privacy-policy).

**Modification to this Policy**  
Hungry Girl may change this policy, but we'll post any changes here. Check back to read them.
